Guide to the Murray Webb Latimer papers, 1930-1980 MS2082
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Papers, 1930-1980; MS2082 Series 1; 39.5 Linear feet
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Proposed Integration of Western Conference Of Teamsters Pension Plan and Central States Pension Plans,Correspondence amd Reports, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L512.11A
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Proposed Integration, of W.C.T. and C.S. Plans,Calculations, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L512.11B
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Proposed Integration of W.C.T. and C.S.,Prudential Material, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L512.11C
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Proposed Integration of W.C.T and C.S., Plans, Agreements Contracts; Kunis, Milliman,Freedman Reports, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L512.11D
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Integration W.C.T. and C.S.,Selection of Corporate Trustee, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L512.11E
  - WESTERN CONFERENCE OF TEAMSTERS: -Housing Study, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L512.12
  - Bureau of National Affairs, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L513
  - Commisioned Officers Association-U.S. Public Health Service, undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L513.a
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES Association: - Governors Committee on Pensions, undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L514
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES Association: -Pension Hearings, 1967 February (Box 48, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L514.1
  - CIVIL SERVICE EMPLOYEES Association: Western Conference of Cannery and Food Process Workers' Unions, Life with Dues Program, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L515.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 49)
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Health Care Plan-Thru 1962 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L516.1
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Health Care Plan, 1963-1970 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L516.1A
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Health Care Plan-Material Concerning Plan, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L516.1B
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Health Care Plan-Employee Benefits Report, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L516.1C
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Health Care Plan-to 12/1973, 1973 February (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L516.1D
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Health Care Plan-Pension Plan, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L516.2a
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Health Care Plan-Pension Plan, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L516.2b
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation,-Pension Plan, Joe Musher's Notes and Calculations, 1966 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L516.2A
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation,-Survivers Benefits, Mortality Only Table, 1966 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L516.2B
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation,-Valuation Censuses, Summaries, 1966 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L516.2C
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation, 1966 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L516.2Ca
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation,-Per Capitas Each Census, 1966 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L516.2D
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation, Service Table, 1966 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L516.2E
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation,-Exposure Study,1933-36, 1966 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L516.2F
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation,-Drafts of Report, 1966 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L516.2G
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Plan Descriptions, Prudential Contracts, undated (Box 49, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L516.2H
  - Papers, undated (Box 50)
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Experience Study and Retirement Test, 1966-1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L516.2I
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Multi Decrement Service Table, 1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: L516.2J
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Per Capita Multi Decrement Table, 1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L516.2K
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Death Benefits, Service Table and Calculations, 1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L516.2L
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Census, Multiplications, 1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L516.2m
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Censuses, 1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L516.2N
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Effects on Pensions to Change From Career to Salary Basis, 1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L516.2Q
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation Notes on Sandia Conference in D.C., 1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L516.2R
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Supplementary Insurance after Retirement, and Test for Retirement Age (worksheets), 1966 April 30-1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L516.3a
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Summary Calculation-Data Processing- Correspondence, 1972 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L516.3a1
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Service Table, Per Capita, 1972 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L516.3a2
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuation -Sandia Experience, 1972 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L516.3a3
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Retired Life Valuation Worksheets, 1970 September 30 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L516.4A
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Retired Valuation, 1973 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L516.4A1
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Retirement Income Plan, Valuation, 1969 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L516.4A2
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Insurance After Retirement, undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L516.4A3
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Group Life Insuranee, Employee Benefits, undated (Box 50, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L516.4A4
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: --Correspondence, Miscl., undated (Box 50, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L5P5.7
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Summaries of Valuation. Results, undated (Box 50, Folder 19)
    Original numbering system:L516. 20
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Pension Plan, Amendments, 1967 January 01 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    Original numbering system:L516.20A
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Valuations-Test of Retirements, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    Original numbering system:L516.21
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -- Retired Life,. Valuation, 1977 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    Original numbering system:L516.22
  - Papers, undated (Box 51)
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: - Pension Fund Plan, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L516.23
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Retirment Plan Tables, 1976-1978 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L516. 24
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Rates and Claims, Valuation Material, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L516.25
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Financial (General), Final Report, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L516.26
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Current Material-Final Result Printouts- valuation Pensions, 1977 December 31 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L516.27
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Pension Valuation,-Service Tables, Rates, Instructions to Dick Muller, 1977 December 31-1978 December 31 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L516.28
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Pension Plans Provisions, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L516.29
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Retirement Income Plan, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L516.31
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Pension Suit, Defendent:Sandia Plaintiff:Edward A. Salazar et al, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L516.32
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Retirement Income Plan, I.R.S. Submission, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L516.33
  - Papers, undated (Box 52)
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Plan Reports, 1970-1978 May 10 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L516.34
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Submission to Nordlaud Firm, Actuarial Report, 1970-1978 October (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L516.35
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Group Health Claim Analysis Report, 1973 March 10-May 31 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L516.36
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Tabulations, 1976 December 31 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L516.37
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Prudential Actuarial Report, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L516.38
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Retirment Plan Reports, 1977 January 01-1978 December 31 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L516.39
  - Papers, undated (Box 53)
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Various Formulae, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L516.41
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Copies of Material Sent to Layman, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L516.42
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Experience-Retired and Active Lives, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L516.43
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Statistical Analysis of Health Care Program-Claims Utilization Report, 1963 October-1964 September (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L516.44
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Utilization Report, 1964 October-1965 September (Box 53, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L516.45
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Utilization Report, 1965 October-1966 September (Box 53, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L516.46
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Benefits Report, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L516.47
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Statistics and Benefits Listing, undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L516.48
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Health Care Plan, Latimer Tables, 1967-1969 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L516.49
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Retirement Income Plan-Triennial Statement ending, 1969 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L516.51
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Retirement Income Plan Exhibit 1, undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L516.52
  - SANDIA CORPORATION: -Pensions, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L516.53
  - Papers, undated (Box 54)
  - FLIGHT ENGINEERS, 1966-1976 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L517.1
  - FLIGHT ENGINEERS, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L517.2
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Preliminary Report on I.W.A. Pension Program, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L518.1 12/14/1960
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Northwest Pension Program, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L518.2
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Northwest Pension Program, Calculations, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L518.2A
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan-Preliminary Investigations, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L518.3
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan-Original Evaluation, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L518.3A 1959
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan-Actuarial Reduction Factors, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L518.3B
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan- Evaluation, 1961 June 30 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L518.3C
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan-, 1961-1962 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L518.3D
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan-Clerical Employees, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L518.3E
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan- Evaluation, 1963 June 30 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L518.3F
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan-Canadian Question, undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L518.3G
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan-General Correspondence, undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L518.4
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan-Van Vick Paper Box Co., undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L518.5
  - INTERNATIONAL WOODWORKERS OF AMERICA: -Staff Pension Plan-Auxiliary Pension Plan, undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L518.6
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -General Correspondence, undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L519
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Term Life Insurance Program, undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L519.1
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Report on Affiliated Ass. Life Insurance Program, 1970 May-1971 March (Box 54, Folder 19)
    Original numbering system:L519.1A
  - Papers, undated (Box 55)
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Specifications, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L519.2
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Report on Insurance Co. Bids, undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L519.4
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Insurance Trust Fund, Prudential Policy, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L519.5
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Insurance Trust Fund, Prudential Policy, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L519.5A
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Insurance Trust Fund, Prudential Policy, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L519.5B
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Insurance Trust Fund, Prudential Policy-Prudential Reports, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L519.5B1
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Insurance Trust Fund,Prudential Policy-Prudential Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L519.5C
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Insurance Trust Fund,Prudential Policy-Prudential Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L519.5C1
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Insurance Trust Fund, Prudential Policy-Prudential Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L519.5C2
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Insurance Trust Fund, Prudential Policy-N.E.A. Minutes, 1963-1965 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L519.5D
  - Papers, undated (Box 56)
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Occupational Liability Program, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L519.6
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Tax Sheltered Annuities, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L519.7
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Affiliated Association Insurance Trust, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L519.8
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Special Services Horace Mann Agreement, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L519.9.
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Corsparisons of Insurance Programs with Horace Mann Education Security Plan, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L519.9,a
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: - Reserve Study Under Insurance Program, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L519.10
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: -Investment Insurance Reserves, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L519.11
  - NATIONAL EDUCATION ASSOCIATION: - Insurance Study, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L519.12
  - Papers, undated (Box 57)
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Valuation, 1962 May 01 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L522.1
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Valuation, 1965 July 01 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L522.1A
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Widow s Benefits, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L522,1B
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Valuation, 1967 September 10 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L522.1C
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Valuation, 1969 September 10 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L522.1D
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-International Calculation of Individual Benefits, undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L522.1E
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Irternational,Valuation, 1970 July 01 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L522.1F
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Intern'l,4 1/2%,Valuation, 1973 July 01-1973 October 11 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L522.1G
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Intern'l, Valuation, 1974 March 31 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L522.1H
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Intern'l, I.R.S. Submissions, undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L522.1J
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Intern'l. ,Valuation, Amended to 1975 (x & E =80,High 4, 1974 October 31 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L522.1KA
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Pension Plans & Amendment Trust & Local 153 Plan, undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L522.1B
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -International Staff Pension Plan-Intern'l Auditors Report, undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L522.1L
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Intern'l Valuations, 1975 December 31-1976 December 31 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L522.1M
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Intern'l Valuations, Report, 1976 July 01-1977 January 01 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L522.1N
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100-Agreement, undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L522.10
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100-Salary Data,(Empolyees), undated (Box 57, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L522.1P
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100I.R.S. Submission, undated (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100- Valuation, 1973 December 31 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    Original numbering system:L522.1R
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100- Val.,(x+t=80,high 4), 1973 December 31 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    Original numbering system:L522.1R1
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100- Val. Staff Pension Plan, 1975 December 31-1976 December 21 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    Original numbering system:L522.1S
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100-N.Y. City Retirement System, undated (Box 57, Folder 22)
    Original numbering system:L522.1T
  - Papers, undated (Box 58)
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100-Staff Pension Plan, Val., 1962 December 01 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L522.2
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100-Staff Pension Plan, Val., 1962 December 01 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L522.2A
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100-Calculations on Individual Benefits, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L522.2B
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100 Valuation, 1969 July 01 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L522.2C
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100- Valuation, 1972 July 01 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100-N.Y. City Private Bus Pension Plan-Cost, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L522.3
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Local 100-N.Y. City Private Bus Pension Plan, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L522.3A
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Private Bus Lines, Valuation, 1969 November 22 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L522.3B
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Private Bus Lines, Valuation, 1967 January 01 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L522.3C
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Transit Authority-Health and Welfare Plan, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L522.4
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Health Insurance Plan, undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L522.4A
  - TRANSPORT WORKERS UNION: -Health Study, Experience Data, undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Papers, undated (Box 59)
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: Preliminary Work, undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L523
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Disability Benefits, undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L523.1
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Death Benefits Study-Death Benefits Study, undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L523.2
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Death Benefits Study-Death Benefits or Pension Reserve Worksheets, undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L523.2a
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Death Benefits Study-Notes and Data-1965-Appendix, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L523.2B
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Death Benefits Study-IBM Tabulations, undated (Box 59, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L523.2C
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Sick leave to Finance Insurance, undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L523.3
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Financing Health Insurance, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L523.4
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Health Insurance Program, undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L523.10
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Listing of Pensioners, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L523.11
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -1% Samples,Cases and Lists, undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L523.12
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Loan Insurance, undated (Box 59, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L523.13v%32882012728252
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Actuarial Materials, undated (Box 59, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L523.14
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Miscl., undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L523.15
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -N.Y. Insurance Dept. -Regulation 33, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L523.16
  - Papers, undated (Box 60)
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L523.17A
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Reports, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L523.17B
  - NEW YORK STATE EMPLOYEES RETIREMENT SYSTEM: -Reports, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L523.17C
  - NEW YORK STATE: -Surviver benefits-Death in Active Service-Widow's Benefits, undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L524.1
  - NEW YORK STATE: -Dependent benefits, Census and Functions, undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L524.2